= kisskh.asia =
"The Last Oat"
(Episode 2: Survival
Rules for the Apocalypse)
You.
Who are you?
What did you do to me?
I'm the one who saved your life.
You'd be dead if it weren't for me.
I bandaged all your wounds.
If I wanted to hurt you,
would I have waited this long?
Who asked you to save me?
What's your real motive for saving me?
What motive could I possibly have?
Even if it were just an
injured stray cat or dog,
I'd save it if I could.
Let alone a living, breathing human being.
Don't even think about getting
any information out of me.
I'll just assume you
hit your head too hard.
I won't hold it against you.
Since I've already brought you back,
I'll take full responsibility for you.
Relax.
This is my secret base.
No one else will come here.
It's easy to die in the apocalypse.
If you really have a death wish,
then how did you get all those wounds?
We're running out of food.
Shouldn't you guys discuss it
over the next couple of days?
It's time to head out.
Now that we have new gear,
maybe we can go a bit further.
And score some good stuff.
Yeah.
This hunting bow packs a real punch.
It'd be great if we could each have one.
Alright.
I'll look into it when the time comes.
Perfect timing.
Before we head out,
I'm going to reinforce the traps.
And forage some wild berries
to stock up for Grandma Qiu.
I won't be back for lunch.
I brought some rations.
Okay.
Then Li Ming and I will hurry
up and make a plan for the trip.
We leave in three days.
Got it.
Stay safe out there.
It's not poison.
See for yourself.
It's legit anti-inflammatory medicine.
Alright then.
Let me check your wounds
and change your bandages first.
How did you get all these injuries?
Why were you passed out in the woods?
I was passing through
while scavenging for supplies.
Ran into a horde of zombies.
Didn't expect there to be a camp nearby.
Then you're pretty lucky.
You ran into me.
Barely.
This camp...
How long has this place you picked been here?
We all spent a long time
searching for before settling down.
This area is easy to
defend and hard to attack.
Your companions
are pretty impressive.
Everyone will definitely
give it their all to survive.
I've also researched a
lot of defensive measures.
We even intercepted
three zombies yesterday.
You're pretty desperate to survive too.
You must really want to live.
Then why didn't you ask
me for help back then?
Instead, you chased me away.
Who knew if you were
going to hurt me or save me?
Now you know I'm not a bad person, right?
Don't move.
The wound is still a bit inflamed.
You need to take
anti-inflammatories to heal faster.
That's more like it.
Why make things hard on yourself?
Let go!
What are you doing?
If you want to survive in the apocalypse,
zombies aren't the only things
you need to guard against.
I can tell who's good and who's bad.
I know you're not a bad person.
But you're not a good one either.
No dinner for you today.
Get some rest and heal up.
What a jerk.
All bark and no bite.
This time we're heading
to the school out east.
Lin Zai,
are you sure there
are still supplies there?
Yeah.
It's just that we were
attacked by zombies back then.
We've already picked the
surrounding areas clean.
We have to take a risk this time.
Alright.
I remember the layout of the school.
But we still need to be extremely careful.
I've got all the gear we need ready.
The traps around the camp
have all been reinforced and checked.
They'll keep Grandma Qiu safe.
Alright, let's head out immediately.
If anything goes wrong,
we pull back at once.
Got it.
Are there zombies?
You're not dead.
I'm here to get my stuff back.
Sorry,
finders keepers.
Stay back!
Don't move!
Don't come any closer!
Give me my backpack
back, exactly as it was.
I know you won't hurt me.
I won't hurt any of you.
As long as you return what's mine.
But if you insist on keeping it,
you're forcing my hand.
Give it all back to him.
What is this junk?
The watch on your wrist is mine too.
It was my idea
to take your things.
But I also saved your life.
Let's call it even.
Just go.
Guangqi.
Calling HQ.
Signal lost.
Unable to establish a stable connection.
Checking the operational
status of other core modules.
Network unavailable.
Positioning module accuracy degraded.
Physiological module detects
surface trauma on the user
and signs of mild infection.
Sample escort protocol updated.
Immune target confirmed.
Sister Chen,
Brother Li,
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
But I really didn't know he'd attack us.
It's all my fault.
Just beat me up.
Let's forget about it this time.
We checked that day,
and that guy really
wasn't bitten by a zombie.
But we still left him to die.
We really didn't need to be so ruthless.
We could have at least left
him some food and medicine.
Lin Zai, you did the right thing.
This incident serves
as a wake-up call for us.
We fight to survive,
not just for ourselves,
but for all of humanity.
If you insist on apologizing,
carry more supplies.
What are you looking at me for?
I'm not helping you this time.
No need.
Brother Li, I just saw a few
bottles of that liquor you like.
I'll grab a few for you
as an apology.
Sounds good.
But you can only bring two bottles at most.
Prioritize essential supplies.
I know.
Minding other people's business, huh.
Run!
Get out of here!